{
  "title": "Level2",
  "description":"1桁 × 1桁\n穴あき",
  "questionCount": 20,
  "questions": [
    {"problem": "?x1=1","answer": 1},
    {"problem": "1x?=1","answer": 1},
    {"problem": "?x2=2","answer": 1},
    {"problem": "1x?=2","answer": 2},
    {"problem": "?x3=3","answer": 1},
    {"problem": "1x?=3","answer": 3},
    {"problem": "?x4=4","answer": 1},
    {"problem": "1x?=4","answer": 4},
    {"problem": "?x5=5","answer": 1},
    {"problem": "1x?=5","answer": 5},
    {"problem": "?x6=6","answer": 1},
    {"problem": "1x?=6","answer": 6},
    {"problem": "?x7=7","answer": 1},
    {"problem": "1x?=7","answer": 7},
    {"problem": "?x8=8","answer": 1},
    {"problem": "1x?=8","answer": 8},
    {"problem": "?x9=9","answer": 1},
    {"problem": "1x?=9","answer": 9},

    {"problem": "?x1=2","answer": 2},
    {"problem": "2x?=2","answer": 1},
    {"problem": "?x2=4","answer": 4},
    {"problem": "2x?=4","answer": 4},
    {"problem": "?x3=6","answer": 2},
    {"problem": "2x?=6","answer": 3},
    {"problem": "?x4=8","answer": 2},
    {"problem": "2x?=8","answer": 4},
    {"problem": "?x5=10","answer": 2},
    {"problem": "2x?=10","answer": 5},
    {"problem": "?x6=12","answer": 2},
    {"problem": "2x?=12","answer": 6},
    {"problem": "?x7=14","answer": 2},
    {"problem": "2x?=14","answer": 7},
    {"problem": "?x8=16","answer": 2},
    {"problem": "2x?=16","answer": 8},
    {"problem": "?x9=18","answer": 2},
    {"problem": "2x?=18","answer": 9},

    {"problem": "3x1=?","answer": 3},
    {"problem": "3x2=?","answer": 6},
    {"problem": "3x3=?","answer": 9},
    {"problem": "3x4=??","answer": 12},
    {"problem": "3x5=??","answer": 15},
    {"problem": "3x6=??","answer": 18},
    {"problem": "3x7=??","answer": 21},
    {"problem": "3x8=??","answer": 24},
    {"problem": "3x9=??","answer": 27},
    {"problem": "4x1=?","answer": 4},
    {"problem": "4x2=?","answer": 8},
    {"problem": "4x3=??","answer": 12},
    {"problem": "4x4=??","answer": 16},
    {"problem": "4x5=??","answer": 20},
    {"problem": "4x6=??","answer": 24},
    {"problem": "4x7=??","answer": 28},
    {"problem": "4x8=??","answer": 32},
    {"problem": "4x9=??","answer": 36},
    {"problem": "5x1=?","answer": 5},
    {"problem": "5x2=??","answer": 10},
    {"problem": "5x3=??","answer": 15},
    {"problem": "5x4=??","answer": 20},
    {"problem": "5x5=??","answer": 25},
    {"problem": "5x6=??","answer": 30},
    {"problem": "5x7=??","answer": 35},
    {"problem": "5x8=??","answer": 40},
    {"problem": "5x9=??","answer": 45},
    {"problem": "6x1=?","answer": 6},
    {"problem": "6x2=??","answer": 12},
    {"problem": "6x3=??","answer": 18},
    {"problem": "6x4=??","answer": 24},
    {"problem": "6x5=??","answer": 30},
    {"problem": "6x6=??","answer": 36},
    {"problem": "6x7=??","answer": 42},
    {"problem": "6x8=??","answer": 48},
    {"problem": "6x9=??","answer": 54},
    {"problem": "7x1=?","answer": 7},
    {"problem": "7x2=??","answer": 14},
    {"problem": "7x3=??","answer": 21},
    {"problem": "7x4=??","answer": 28},
    {"problem": "7x5=??","answer": 35},
    {"problem": "7x6=??","answer": 42},
    {"problem": "7x7=??","answer": 49},
    {"problem": "7x8=??","answer": 56},
    {"problem": "7x9=??","answer": 63},
    {"problem": "8x1=?","answer": 8},
    {"problem": "8x2=??","answer": 16},
    {"problem": "8x3=??","answer": 24},
    {"problem": "8x4=??","answer": 32},
    {"problem": "8x5=??","answer": 40},
    {"problem": "8x6=??","answer": 48},
    {"problem": "8x7=??","answer": 56},
    {"problem": "8x8=??","answer": 64},
    {"problem": "8x9=??","answer": 72},
    {"problem": "9x1=?","answer": 9},
    {"problem": "9x2=??","answer": 18},
    {"problem": "9x3=??","answer": 27},
    {"problem": "9x4=??","answer": 36},
    {"problem": "9x5=??","answer": 45},
    {"problem": "9x6=??","answer": 54},
    {"problem": "9x7=??","answer": 63},
    {"problem": "9x8=??","answer": 72},
    {"problem": "9x9=??","answer": 81}
  ]
}
